svnlabs.com 2019-07-22

# S V N Labs Softwares | Privacy Policy

SVNLabs strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of  
Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized  
experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (svnlabs,  
svnlabs@gmail.com, Jaipur, +919928673578) subject to the terms  
of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email  
address to any unauthorized third party.

How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are  
visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the  
services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information  
when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request  
certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You  
may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and  
contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of  
our site. Like most Web sites, this Website also collects information  
automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be  
transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your  
Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and  
hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may  
store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter  
that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times  
you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we  
adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through  
other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with  
information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept  
cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of  
the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we  
may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your  
preferences.

What we do with the information we collect

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit  
and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your  
privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify  
you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information  
about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other  
users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages  
are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated  
Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business  
partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally  
Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you  
individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on this Website  
to communicate with you about your registration and customization  
preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and  
products offered by this Website and other topics we think you might  
find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by this Website may also  
be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site  
administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions,  
administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications  
with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the  
operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access  
such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law.  
In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business,  
we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses.  
In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred  
assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court  
order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do  
so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to  
us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it  
appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice  
prior to disclosure in such cases.

Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements

This Website expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect  
the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties,  
including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content  
providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and  
data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit  
to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a this  
Website page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a  
third party. Also, through this Website you may be introduced to, or be  
able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or  
sweepstakes offered by other parties. This Website is not responsible  
for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the  
applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing  
information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third  
parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some  
of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some  
of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies  
that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a  
particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site  
may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or  
other technology to gather information. This Website does not control  
the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting  
information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such  
third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally  
Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that  
information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by  
third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited  
messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are  
beyond the control of this Website and this policy.

Children

This Website does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally  
Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as  
permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a  
child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that  
information immediately. If you believe This Website has any information  
from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.

Changes to this Policy

This Website reserves the right to change this policy at any time.  
Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of  
our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you  
accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change  
is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at  
the time the information was collected.
